Guide to the Bruce Davidson photographs, 1955-2008 RL.11753
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- England, Scotland and Wales, 1960-1965; 26 prints
  - UK. London. Bus conductor woman with ticket machine, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 19 7/8 x 15 7/8 inches (50.48 x 40.32 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0065)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 60-22-5/19; 50644 [189]
  - UK. Hastings. Children playing on rocks, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 15 7/8 x 19 7/8 inches (40.32 x 50.48 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0066)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 60-22-26/20A; 50659 [189]
  - UK. Brighton. "I love a phantom", 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 19 7/8 x 15 7/8 inches (50.48 x 40.32 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0067)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 60-22-30/34; 50661 [189]
  - UK, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 19 7/8 x 15 7/8 inches (50.48 x 40.32 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0068)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 60-22-77/13; 50634 [189]
  - UK, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 19 7/8 x 15 7/8 inches (50.48 x 40.32 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0069)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 60-22-50/25; 50642 [189]
  - GB. Wales. Boy wearing a mask, 1965; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0070)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 65-52-1/31; 52454 [153]
  - GB. Wales. A bride walking in field, 1965; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0071)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 65-52-5/27; 52474 [153]
  - Great Britain. Wales, 1965; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0072)
    Title source: Magnum Photos (title comes from similar images of horse; title on site of this image is "Welsh miners.") Subject is a horse lying down in a field. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 65-52-6/22; 52525 [153]
- France: La nature de Paris, 2005-2006; 25 prints
  This selection of black-and-white images, all shot in Paris during Davidson's return visit in 2005 and 2006, focus chiefly on Paris gardens, monuments, and public spaces. Photographs from this period, some of which are in this series, were featured in a 2007 exhibit titled "La nature de Paris." Titles, when present, are taken from the print versos or from the Magnum Photos website.
  - No known title, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0073)
    Paris, France [source of note: donor inventory]. Other legacy identifiers: 42322 [36]
  - Emelyne, Palais Royal, 2005; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0074)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2005003W00150/48;42290 [36]
  - Jardin de Luxembourg, 2005; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0075)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 42191 [36]
  - Jardin du Luxembourg sculpture, 2005; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0076)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2005003W00102/2;42195 [36]
  - Julie, Jardin de Luxembourg, 2005; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0077)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2005003W0095/1;42196 [36]
  - Buttes Montmartre, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0078)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2006-3-268/8; 42218 [36]
  - Grand Palais, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0079)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2006-3-261/11; 42202 [36]
  - Grand Palais, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0080)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2006-3-269/3; 42369 [36]
  - Jardin du Luxembourg, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0081)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 06-3-92/9; 42356 [36]
  - Jardin du Luxembourg, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0082)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 06-3-249/4; 42365 [36]
  - Jardin Marco Polo, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0083)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 06-003-W00016/12; 42374 [36]
  - Jardin Saint-Gilles Grand-Veneur, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0084)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 03-6-236/11 [may be typo - 06-3-236/11]; 42235 [36]
  - Parc André Citroën, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0085)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 06-3-235/3; 42379 [36]
  - Parc De Bagatelle, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0086)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 6-3-142/5; 42298 [36]
  - Parc De Bagatelle, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0087)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 06-3-125/4; 42230 [36]
  - Rue Du Tolbiac, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0088)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 06-3-150/8; 42213 [36]
  - Square Jean XXIII Notre Dame, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0089)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 06-3-101/11; 42206 [36]
  - Trees in front of the Louvre, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0090)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2006-003-W00062/6; 42305 [36]
  - Trees reflected in pond by Medici statue, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0091)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2006-003-W00068/1; 42207 [36]
  - The Eiffel Tower, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 19 7/8 x 15 7/8 inches (50.48 x 40.32 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0092)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 05-3-204/1; 50710 [190]
  - No known title, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 19 7/8 x 15 7/8 inches (50.48 x 40.32 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0093)
    Paris, France. Other legacy identifiers: DEK 14/2/8EB; 50707 [190]
  - No known title, 2005; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0094)
    Paris, France. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 05-3-110/10; 48417 [113]
  - Eiffel Tower, 2005; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 23 7/8 x 19 7/8 inches (60.64 x 50.48 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0095)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: 46630 [141]
  - Tuileries Gardens, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 23 7/8 x 19 7/8 inches (60.64 x 50.48 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0096)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: 46621 [141]
  - Paris, 2006; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 23 7/8 x 19 7/8 inches (60.64 x 50.48 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0097)
    Title source: Magnum Photos caption. Other legacy identifiers: 46631 [141]
- France: Paris en hiver [Paris in Winter], 1962; 6 prints
  A visit to Paris in the 1960s resulted in a portfolio of black-and-white photographs which Davidson entitled "Paris en hiver," or "Winter in Paris," of which these prints are a part. Titles, when present, are taken from the print versos.
  - Paris. Enfants jeux extérieurs, 1962; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0098)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 62-6-21/29A-30; 43536 [61]
  - France. Paris en hiver, 1962; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0099)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 62-6-15/23-23A; 43519 [61]. Stamp on print verso is from the Magnum Paris Library archives.
  - France. White, 1962; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0100)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 62-6-56/29-30; 45878 [128]
  - Paris, 1962; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0101)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 62-6-57/26; PR002686; 45897 [128]
  - No known title, 1962; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0102)
    Paris, France. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 62-6-47/9A-10; 43844 [61]
  - No known title, 1962; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0103)
    Paris, France. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 62-6-40/29A-30; 43501 [61]
- France: Valentino Haute Couture, 1999; 2 prints
  This pair of photographs is part of a commercial assignment documenting fashion designer Valentino's fall 1999 couture show in Paris.
  - France. Paris. A model is fitted for the Valentino Haute Couture Fall/Winter show by seamstresses at Place Vendôme, Valentino's studio, 1999; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 12 x 9 1/2 inches (30.48 x 24.13 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0104)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 14; DAB990009W00007/18; D99N545WL/14; 43194 [59]. Print also bears a barcode.
  - France. Paris. Model Stella Tennant is fitted for the Valentino Haute Couture Fall/Winter show by seamstresses at Place Vendôme, Valentino's studio, 1999; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 12 x 9 1/2 inches (30.48 x 24.13 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0105)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 13; DAB990009W00042/20A; D99N545WL/17; 43189 [59]
- France: Widow of Montmartre, 1956; 3 prints
  Davidson shot this early black-and-white study of life in Paris from 1955-1956 during an extended stay in bohemian Montmartre, a Paris arrondisement favored by artists. The elderly woman portrayed in this series was the widow of an Impressionist painter, Léon Fauché.
  - France. Paris. Mme. Fauché, the widow of an impressionist painter, 1956; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0106)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 56-3-2/16; 52888 [157]
  - Widow of Montmartre, 1956; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0107)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 57-2-2/24; 4/3/14; 52857 [157]
  - No known title, 1956; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0108)
    Widow of Montmartre series. Other legacy identifiers: 48863 [120]
- Italy, 1961, 2000; 7 prints
  The photographs taken in Sicily were taken by Davidson during an early 1960s European trip, while the single shot of Venice was taken in 2000.
  - No known title, 1961; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0109)
    Woman on the beach, Sicily. Location source: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: 61-13-43-22; 46900 [137]
  - No known title, 1961; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0110)
    Woman on the beach, Sicily. Location source: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: 61-13-43-26; 46901 [137]
  - No known title, 1961; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0111)
    Orange tree with temple in background, Sicily. Location source: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: 61-13-61-18; 46909 [137]
  - No known title, 1961; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0112)
    Landscape, Sicily. Location source: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: 61-13-5-28A; 46910 [137]
  - No known title, 1961; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0113)
    Shepherd and sheep on crest of hill, Sicily. Location source: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: 61-13-22-18A; 46914 [137]
  - No known title, 1961; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0114)
    Boy and girl in chairs at wedding, Sicily. Location source: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: 61-13-21-21; 46941 [137]
  - No known title, 2000; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0115)
    Venice. Location source: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2000-11; 45498 [71]
- New York, 1990-2001; 4 prints
  These assorted images of New York City were taken by Bruce Davidson over the span of roughly a decade.
  - USA. New York. Seaport, 1997; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0116)
    Title source: print verso. An additional note reads "Animaux chiens," in reference to the dog in the photograph. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 97-4-21/14; 42697 [56]
  - No known title, 1990; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0117)
    Probably Lower East Side. Other legacy identifiers: 90-2-44/36; 44648 [67]
  - No known title, 1996; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0118)
    New York Harbor. Location source: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 96-5-171/35; 45030 [69]
  - No known title, 2001; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0119)
    Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2001-029W-002/35; 42708 [56]
  - No known title, 2001; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0120)
    Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2001-029W-002/16; 42707 [56]
- New York: Central Park, 1963, 1991-1992; 27 prints
  This series takes its name from a Bruce Davidson photobook by the same title published in 1995. Starting in the early 1960s and continuing into the 2000s, the photographer explored the human interactions and spontaneously formed and extraordinarily diverse communities of New York City's Central Park. Almost all titles are taken from the Magnum Photos website.
  - No known title, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0121)
    Other legacy identifiers: DAB 92-5-651/12 43374 [60]
  - No known title, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0122)
    Other legacy identifiers: DAB 92-5-587/8; 43388 [60]
  - Central Park, 1963; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 13 7/8 inches (27.94 x 35.24 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0123)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: B 1998303; 46795 [136]. Stamp is from the Magnum Photo Library, New York.
  - USA. New York City. Lola and the birds in Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0124)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 92-5-49/34A-35; 41749 [34]
  - USA. New York City. Newlyweds in Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0125)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 92-5-39/17A; 41899 [34]
  - No known title, 1991; Cibachrome color print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0126)
    An image from the same portrait shoot of an older Black woman embracing an elderly woman in a [wheel?]chair is titled Central Park, 1991. Other legacy identifiers: 50455 [185]
  - No known title, 1992; Cibachrome color print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0127)
    Other legacy identifiers: 50470 [185]
  - USA. New York City. Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0128)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 92-5-513/1-2; 6/18/6; 41925 [34]
  - USA. New York City. Central Park. Angel of the Waters Fountain at Bethesda Terrace, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0129)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 92-5-1485/28; 41812 [34]
  - USA. New York City. Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0130)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 92-5-609/12; 41842 [34]
  - USA. New York City. Baby robin with mother and worm in Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0131)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 92-5-667/19A-20; 41852 [34]
  - USA. New York City. Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0132)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 92-5-686/3-4; 41884 [34]
  - USA. New York City. Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0133)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 92-5-1286/7-8; 41889 [34]
  - USA. New York City. Central Park. Family picnic under a linden tree, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0134)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 92-5-1341/2; 41795 [34]
  - USA. New York City. Birdwatchers in Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0135)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 41764 [34]]
  - USA. New York City. Couple at roots of tree in Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0136)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 1334-6; 49282 [124]
  - USA. New York City. Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0137)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 49279 [124]
  - USA. New York City. Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 19 7/8 x 16 inches (50.48 x 40.64 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0138)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 92-5-1252/5; 50009 [171]
  - USA. New York City. Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 16 x 20 inches (40.64 x 50.80 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0139)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 92-5-115/30A-31; 50007 [171]
  - USA. New York City. Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 16 x 20 inches (40.64 x 50.80 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0140)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 49325 [124]
  - USA. New York City. Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 20 x 15 7/8 inches (50.80 x 40.32 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0141)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 92N-005-1398/12; 49291 [124]
  - USA. New York City. Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 16 x 20 inches (40.64 x 50.80 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0142)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 41509 [32]
  - USA. New York City. Central Park, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 19 7/8 x 16 inches (50.48 x 40.64 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0143)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 41491 [32]
  - No known title, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 16 x 20 inches (40.64 x 50.80 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0144)
    Other legacy identifiers: 41493 [32]
  - No known title, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 16 x 20 inches (40.64 x 50.80 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0145)
    Other legacy identifiers: 41496 [32]
  - No known title, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 16 x 20 inches (40.64 x 50.80 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0146)
    Other legacy identifiers: 41499 [32]
  - No known title, 1992; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 16 x 20 inches (40.64 x 50.80 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0147)
    Other legacy identifiers: 41502 [32]
- New York: East 100th Street, 1960, 1966; 4 prints
  These black-and-white images, all taken by Bruce Davidson with a large-format camera on the streets of East Harlem, can be found in the photobook by the same title, East 100th Street, published in 1970. These are among Davidson's earliest photographs of New York City life. Most titles, when present, are taken from Magnum Photos website.
  - Large rat takes advantage of pile of garbage, 1960; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 9 7/8 x 8 inches (25.08 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0148)
    Title source: print verso. Magnum Photos title reads: "East 100th Street." Other legacy identifiers: 60-46-374/3; 33418; 215-C-75; 51540 [143]. Print verso heavily marked with Magnum stamps.
  - No known title, 1966; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0149)
    New York City, East 100 St. [from donor inventory]. Other legacy identifiers: 53183 [89]
  - USA. New York City. East 100th Street, 1966; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0150)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 66-46-481/3; 52549 [154]
  - USA. New York City. East 100th Street, 1966; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0151)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 66-46-221/3; 52570 [154]
- New York: Garden Cafeteria, 1973; 6 prints
  These black-and-white portraits of restaurant customers were taken in the Garden Cafeteria, a popular eatery in the center of a Jewish community in the Lower East Side of New York City. It was long known as a meeting place for intellectuals and literati. Titles, when present, are taken from the Magnum Photos website.
  - No known title, 1973; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0152)
    Garden Cafeteria series [source of note: donor inventory]. Other legacy identifiers: PF105718; 52194 [150]
  - No known title, 1973; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0153)
    Garden Cafeteria series [source of note: donor inventory]. Other legacy identifiers: 52210 [150]
  - USA. New York City. The Cafeteria, 1973; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0154)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 73-13-1A/17-18; 52243 [150]
  - USA. New York City. The Cafeteria, 1973; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0155)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 73-13-6b/7-6a; 52153 [150]